Contact

dfgd08555@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/roei-redler (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Dynamics CRM Microsoft Power Automate Microsoft Power Platform

Languages

Hebrew (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Microsoft Certified: Power Platform Solution Architect Expert

Microsoft Certified: Power Platform Fundamentals

MongoDB Essentials - Understand the Basics of MongoDB

Create Analytics Dashboard with PowerBi and Tableau

Microsoft Certified: Power Platform Functional Consultant Associate

Roei Redler

CRM Dynamics specialist || Studying Business Administration in Information Systems

Center District, Israel

Summary

Student at third year undergraduate degree in Business Administration specializing in information systems.

professional in Microsoft applications and especially in Dynamics Crm and Excel.

I have a great bond to the world of data and believe it is a very powerful tool.

Also, Always responds positively to challenges and tries to find technological solutions.

Experience

abra Microsoft Solutions CRM Dynamics specialist August 2022 - Present (5 months) Israel

abra Microsoft Solutions is a Gold Partner of Microsoft

MalamTeam
CRM Dynamics specialist
February 2022 - July 2022 (6 months)
Central, Israel

Malam Systems is a Gold Partner of Microsoft

Requirements:

Characterization and analysis of the CRM DYNAMICS system

High level & Detail design

Matrix work

Working with databases

Managerial orientation with experience in project management

Experience with ENTERPRISE organizations

Working with managers and senior executives

Working with Microsoft power platform

Agile working method

Israeli Ministry of Defense

3 years 3 months

Shift Manager/Vice Manager

December 2020 - January 2022 (1 year 2 months)

Central, Israel

Shift Manager and Vice Manager of the Ministry of Defense Service Center Management of 20 employees.

The role requires:

- Interpersonal communication and high emotional intelligence.
- Create reports and track data.
- Process testing and analysis capability, flexibility of thought and function.
- High ability to motivate employees.
- Distinguishing between the main thing and the bland.
- Systemic and business vision.
- Computer operations and systems including Office, knowledge management systems, BI systems, CRM Dynamics 2011, quality control systems and listening management.
- Dealing with stress situations and dealing with several factors at the same time.
- -Transfer training to employees.

Call Center Customer Service Representative November 2018 - December 2020 (2 years 2 months)

Central, Israel

Customer Service Representative at the Ministry of Defense Call Center The role requires:

- Dealing with stress situations and dealing with several factors at the same time.
- Quick learning
- Ecstations on financial matters
- Organization and order
- Operations of computer software such as: Office, CRM Dynamics 2011.
- Ability to work independently.
- High human relations.
- Remote user support.

Israeli Air Force Aircraft Interceptor August 2015 - March 2018 (2 years 8 months) Fighter in the IDF Air Defense Unit

Education

Ono Academic College

Student, BA in Business Administration in Information Systems · (2019 - 2022)

Premilitary Academy "Elisha" graduate, Bible/Biblical Studies · (2014 - 2015)

Amit Kfar Ganim Yeshiva graduate, A high school diploma · (2008 - 2014)